http://www.hngirlscouts.org/en/about-girl-scouts/about-hornets-nest/privacy-policy.html

MY GS
ABOUT USWho We AreThe Case for Girl Scouts Our HistoryAbout Hornets' NestHours of OperationBoard of DirectorsMeet Our StaffEmployment OpportunitiesCouncil Service UnitsNewsForms and DocumentsLead Like A Girl Scout JoinContact UsRenew ACTIVITIES COOKIES ADULTS PROGRAM CAMP DONATE MY GS
Join
Forms
Shop
Contact Us
Interest Form
En Español
Who We AreThe Case for Girl Scouts Our HistoryAbout Hornets' NestHours of OperationBoard of DirectorsMeet Our StaffEmployment OpportunitiesCouncil Service UnitsNewsForms and DocumentsLead Like A Girl Scout JoinContact UsRenew
About Us
About Hornets' NestPrivacy Policy
Privacy Policy
Welcome to the official website of Girl Scouts, Hornets’ Nest Council
(GSHNC). This website is owned and operated by Girl Scouts, Hornets’
Nest Council, a 501(c)(3) non-profit organization headquartered in
Charlotte, NC.
Our Commitment to Privacy Girl Scouts, Hornets’ Nest
Council is committed to protecting the privacy of our visitors. This
privacy policy discloses how we collect, protect and use information
you provide online, as well as how we protect children's privacy. By
using pages on our site, you are accepting the practices described in
this Privacy Policy. If our policy changes, we will let you know by
posting changes here. However, we will treat all personal information
we collect in accordance with the privacy notice in effect at the time
the information is collected.
Information We Collect Girl Scouts, Hornets’ Nest
Council uses its best efforts to respect and protect the privacy and
personal information of our online visitors. We do not collect
personally identifiable information from individuals, unless they
provide it voluntarily and knowingly. This means we do not require you
to register or provide information to view our site. To process online
transactions, we do collect identifiable data including names,
addresses, zip/postal codes, email addresses, etc. when voluntarily
submitted by a customer. This information is used solely by GSHNC in
the internal operations of our site. We do not sell information to
third parties and will only share personally identifiable information
with third parties when (i) the person submitting the information
authorizes us to share; (ii) sharing the information is necessary to
process a credit card transaction, or (iii) we are required to share
by law.
Children's Policy COPPA (Children's Online Privacy
Protection Act) was established to promote safe internet usage by
children. The Girl Scouts, Hornets’ Nest Council website uses its best
efforts to comply with the COPPA guidelines on data collection,
particularly from children. We encourage you to read more about COPPA.
Use of Cookies Visitors should be aware that
non-personal information and data may be automatically collected by
GSHNC’s site through the use of “cookies.” "Cookies" are
small data files placed on your computer by our site, used by your
browser. Cookies enable us to track features and content you like best
to provide online shopping or donations. Cookies may be used to store
information about the parts of our site you visit to help you navigate
our site more easily. Most browsers are initially set to accept
cookies. If you wish, you can set your browser to refuse cookies and
will be able to use most areas of our website.
Credit Card Safety Protecting the safety of your
credit card information is important, so we use Secure Sockets Layer
(SSL) technology to protect the security of your credit card
information as it is transmitted to us. SSL is the industry standard
in internet encryption technology, which is a highly sophisticated
method of scrambling data as it travels from your computer to our
website servers. Your credit card number is encrypted when you place
an order and when a transfer is made to participating merchants. GSHNC
limits access to personal information to employees with a specific
need for this information. It is important for you to protect against
unauthorized access to your password and to your computer. Be sure to
sign off when finished using a shared computer. If you are under 18,
you need parent/guardian permission to use a credit card to make
purchases online.
Links to other Websites and Services This site may be
linked to other sites and services that are not maintained by GSHNC.
These websites have their own privacy policies, which you should
review prior to visiting them. We have no responsibility for linked
websites and provide links solely for the convenience of our visitors.
Internal Security The safety and security of your online
experience is of utmost concern. We ensure appropriate physical,
electronic, and managerial procedures are in place to safeguard and
help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security and correctly
use the information we collect online.
How to Contact Us If you have any questions about our
Privacy Policy, please contact us at:
